ultralingua.com 2012-06-14

# Privacy Policy | Ultralingua | Ultralingua

The information below explains why we ask for your personal information and how we use it. If you have any questions, you can email us at [privacy@ultralingua.com](mailto:privacy@ultralingua.com).

**If you subscribe to our newsletter:**

If you want to receive our e-newsletter, we’ll need your email address to deliver it. We will never give your email address to anyone else.

You can subscribe to our monthly e-newsletter by providing your email address at the bottom of any page on our website. To get a look at what kind of content you’ll receive in the newsletter, check out our archive [here](http://www.ultralingua.com/press/newsletters "View our newsletter archive.").

When you subscribe, you'll receive a confirmation email which will ask you to validate your request. This prevents others from signing you up for our newsletter without your permission. If you don't see the confirmation message, you may want to check your spam folder just in case.

You can unsubscribe at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link in the newsletter, or by emailing newsletter@ultralingua.com. If you unsubscribe, your email address is automatically removed from our list and we won’t contact you again.

**If you purchase something from our site:**

We use a third-party provider called [cleverbridge](https://www.cleverbridge.com/243/?scope=opprivacy&id=aMNpSJDNF4 "View the cleverbridge privacy policy here.") for our secure online shopping cart and payment processing. All personal information necessary to make a purchase is available to them for security purposes. They’ll process your payment, which means we can’t view any of your payment information.

When you purchase something from our site, cleverbridge tells us your name, email address, and a list of products included in your order so we can provide support if you have a technical problem later on.

**Do we share your personal information with anyone else?**

No way.

**How do we use cookies?**

We use them in our online dictionary to reload your last dictionary choice and to remember that you are still logged in. Additionally, we use cookies to remember what’s in your shopping cart so it doesn’t empty itself if you click “continue shopping”. We do not use them to track your personal information.

**How do we safeguard the information above?**

We store your information in electronic form and take precautions to protect these records from misuse or unauthorized access via procedural electronic safeguards. When the information above is no longer needed, we remove it from our records.

**Do you have any comments or questions?**

If you have any other privacy-related questions, you can contact [privacy@ultralingua.com](mailto:privacy@ultralingua.com).

We may amend this policy from time to time, to make sure that it is accurate and up-to-date. If we do, we’ll share the changes with you here.
